等一下 你说这个女演员
Wait a minute. You're telling me this actress person...
是唯一你渴望着她 她却不要你的女人
...is the only woman you ever wanted who didn't want you back?
对
Yeah.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你的人生都是这样吗
Is this what it's like to be you?
- 你真的爱上她了吧   - 你不懂
- Wow, you're really crazy about her, huh?     - Oh. You have no idea.
我们在舞台上 我得吻她跟触碰她
And when we're on-stage, I get to kiss her and touch her.
然后她跟导演回家
But then she goes home with the director...
那像是有人把我的心挖了出来一样
...and it's like somebody's ripping out my heart.
很高兴你也有这种感觉
Oh, it's so great to see you feeling like this.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
摩妮卡 今天早上爸打电话来
Monica, uh, Dad called this morning...
席薇亚阿姨过世了
...and, uh, Aunt Sylvia passed away.
太棒了
Yes. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们都很震惊
We were all pretty shaken up about it.
等一下 我是不是漏掉了什么事
Wait, am I missing something?
我以为死亡只会带来悲伤
Because I always thought death was supposed to be sad, in a way.
席薇亚阿姨
Well, uh, Aunt Sylvia was...
不是个好人
...well, not a nice person.
没错 她是个残忍爱挑剔的老太婆
No, she was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
我很遗憾她过世了
And I'm sorry she died.
爸说我得到娃娃屋了吗
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
- 你得到娃娃屋了   - 我得到娃娃屋了
- You get the dollhouse.     - I get the dollhouse.
娃娃住的房子 超棒的
Wow. A house for dolls. That is so cool.
小时候我只有一个桶子
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
菲比 你把娃娃放在桶子里
Uh, Pheebs, you had a barrel for a dollhouse?
不 只有桶子
No, just a barrel.
你知道吗 你可以玩我的娃娃屋
You know what? You can play with my dollhouse.
- 真的吗   - 随时都可以
- Really? Really?     - Any time you want.
小时候我只想玩这个娃娃屋
When I was younger, all I wanted to do was to play with this dollhouse.
不行 它只能远观 不能亵玩
But no. It was to be looked at, but never played with.
以前我奶奶也是那么说我的
My grandmother used to say that exact same thing to me.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
（布鲁明岱尔百货公司）
- 嘿 苏菲   - 嘿 瑞秋
- Hey, Sophie.     - Hey, Rach.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.   - Hey.
谢谢你请我吃午餐 钱德 你不必陪我走回办公室
Thanks for lunch, Chandler. You didn't have to walk me here.
别客气 不成问题
Oh, that's okay. No problem.
甜心 你知道我们不会把女用内衣放在办公室里
Honey, you do realize we don't keep the women's lingerie here in the office.
对 我知道
Yes, I realize that.
- 夏季型录   - 那才是我要的东西
- Summer catalog.     - That's the stuff.
瑞秋 我要凡赛斯的发票
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
你好 你不是我的员工
Hello. You don't work for me.
乔安娜 他是我的朋友钱德宾 乔安娜
Joanna, this is my friend Chandler Bing. Joanna.
宾 非常不错的姓氏
Bing? Heh. That's a great name.
谢谢 盖尔语的意思是"你的火鸡熟了"
Thanks, it's Gaelic for, "Thy turkey's done."
- 我得走了 幸会   - 幸会
- So, uh, I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you.     - You too.
再见 钱德
Bye, Chandler.
他是怎么了
So, uh, what's wrong with him?
没事 他本来就呆呆的 我几乎不再注意到这一点
Oh, nothing. He's just goofy like that. I actually hardly notice it anymore.
不 我是说他已婚或有交往对象吗
Oh, no, no, no. I mean, is he, um, married or involved with anyone?
不 他是单身 也没有跟任何人交往
No, no. He's not married or involved with anyone.
瑞秋
Oh, Rachel...
你知道吗 算了
Actually, you know what? Forget it.
- 如果你要的话 我能帮你约他   - 真的吗
- I'll ask him for you if you want me to.     - Would you?
那不会显得我太悲惨绝望吗
Or is it just too sad and desperate...
就跟苏菲会做的事一样
...you know, something that Sophie would do?
- 我在这里   - 我知道
- I am here.     - I know that.
你们看
Look at it.
壁纸有点褪色 没关系
Wallpaper's a little faded. That's okay.
地毯有点松了
Carpet's a little loose.
硬木地板
Hardwood floors?
- 嘿   - 哈罗
- Hey. Oh!     - Hello.
喔 摩妮卡
Oh, Monica.
- 好漂亮   - 我知道
- It's so beautiful.     - I know.
- 我来了 准备开始玩了   - 好吧
- So I'm here, ready to play. Hee-hee.     - Okay.
我带了一些东西来装饰娃娃屋 看吧
I brought a bunch of stuff for the house, so check it out. Ha, ha.
这是什么
What's this?
那是狗 每间屋子都该有狗
That's a dog. Every house should have a dog.
我不要会在屋顶尿尿的狗
Not one that can pee on the roof.
或许他会这么大 因为屋子是用辐射废弃物盖成的
Well, maybe it's so big because the house was built on radioactive waste.
这是为了预防屋子打喷嚏吗
And is this in case the house sneezes?
不 那是阁楼的鬼魂
No. No, that's the ghost for the attic.
- 我不要鬼   - 没有人要鬼
- I don't want a ghost.     - Well, nobody wants a ghost.
但你有一个鬼
But you've got one...
因为屋子盖在古老的印第安坟场上
...because the house is sitting on an ancient Indian burial ground.
等一下 屋子用辐射废弃物盖成
Wait a minute. The house was built on radioactive waste...
而且位于古老印第安坟场
...and an ancient Indian burial ground?
不可能会有那种事
Ha, ha. That would never happen.
好吧 显然你不太了解美国政府
Okay, obviously you don't know much about the U.S. Government. Ha, ha.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 我得跟你谈一谈   - 没问题 什么事
- I need to talk to you.     - Sure. What's up?
抱歉 我是指钱德
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
我知道
Heh. I know.
如果有事的话…
Well, if something comes up...
我很高兴你们度过尴尬期了
Well, I'm glad you guys are past that little awkward phase.
好吧 我的上司 乔安娜  你离开后
Okay. My boss, Joanna. When you left...
她开始问起关于你的问题
...she started asking questions about you.
看上眼了
Ha, ha. Liked what she saw, huh?
她喜欢我的活力 对吧
Dug my action, did she?
打探小钱钱的事
Checking out the Chan Chan Man.
那真的…
That was...
太不可思议了
...surreal.
好吧 你觉得呢 你有兴趣吗
Okay, what do you think? You interested at all?
对 她蛮酷的 也很迷人 我愿意
Yeah, she seemed cool, attractive. I'll do it.
谢谢你 钱德 这太棒了 她一定会爱死我的
Oh, thank you, Chandler. This is great. She's gonna love me.
好吧 恐龙攻击 快点 大家躲进屋里
Okay, dinosaur attack. Quick, everybody into the house. Aah!
好了 菲比 就那样 你知道吗 好吗
All right, Phoebe, you know what? That's it. That's it. All right?
不准有恐龙 鬼或大狗 好吗
No dinosaurs, no ghosts, no giant dogs, okay?
它们的尺寸不对 不是维多利亚时代风格 完全不配
They're not the right size, they're not Victorian, and they just don't go.
好吧
Okay.
Fine.
来吧 恐龙 没想像力的屋子不欢迎我们
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome in the house of no imagination.
菲比 既然我们谈到这一点
Uh, Pheebs, while we're hovering around the subject...
我只是想说恐龙不会汪汪叫
...I just have to say that dinosaurs, they don't go, "Ruff."
小恐龙就会
The little ones do.
（路西尔洛泰剧场）
- 凯特   - 早安
- Hey, Kate.     - Morning.
听着 我去了你提过的那家餐厅
Listen, I, uh, went to that restaurant you talked about...
宝贝
Hey, lovely.
来吧 我得跟你谈一下
Come, talk to me for a minute.
我吃了那里的食物 真的很好吃 我点了鱼
And I ate the food. It was good. I had the fish.
对 那真的很不错
Yeah, it was pretty good. Yeah.
嗨
Hi.
我是萝伦 凯特的替补演员
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
嘿 乔伊•崔比亚尼
Oh. Hey. Joey Tribbiani.
我知道 我是你的超级粉丝
I know. I'm a big fan of yours.
什么
What?
以前我会调整课表 只为了在"我们的日子"
I used to, um, schedule my classes so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
看到德瑞克•雷莫瑞医生
...on Days of our Lives.
不可能 真的吗
Get out of here. Really?
当然
Absolutely.
后来他们把你推下电梯井
Oh, but then they went and dropped you down that elevator shaft.
对 他们真的杀了我
Yeah, they gave me the shaft, all right.
你真的好好笑
You're so funny.
听着 彩排后你要做什么
Listen, um, what are you doing after rehearsal?
你要去喝一杯吗
Do you wanna get a drink or something?
那个嘛…
Well, uh...
没问题 喝一杯是个好点子
Yeah. Yeah, sure. A drink sounds great.
- 酷啊 到时候见   - 好的
- Cool. I'll see you then.     - Okay. All right.
好吧 该开始演戏了 我会说话的道具们
All right. It's time to act, my talking props.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
大家看吧 看看我的新娃娃屋
Look, everybody. Look at my new dollhouse.
看吧
Ha, ha. Look, look.
这是什么
Hey, what's this?
好吧 那是用溜滑梯代替楼梯 看吧
Oh, okay. It's a slide instead of stairs. Look.
非常有趣 菲比
Very interesting, Phoebe.
这是什么
What's this?
甘草糖房间 家具都可以吃
The licorice room. You can eat all the furniture.
客人来的时候 可以睡在糖果床上面
And when guests come over, they can stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
这是史上最酷的屋子
This is the coolest house ever.
谁要跟我一起到芬芳疗室
Hey. Does anyone want to join me in the Aroma Room?
- 好吧   - 我要
- All right.     - I would.
各位
Hey, guys? Guys.
你们看到我的新瓷器柜了吗
Did you see my new china cabinet?
看吧
Watch. Watch.
还有呢
And? And?
我爸的房子也会那样
Hey, my father's house does that.
好吧 怎么样 快告诉我
Okay, how did it go? Tell me everything.
电影非常不错
Well, the movie was great...
晚餐非常不错 凉爽的纽约夜晚是最棒的
...dinner was great, and there's nothing like a cool, crisp New York evening.
当然我没办法好好享受 因为乔安娜超无聊的
Of course, I didn't get to enjoy any of that because Joanna's such a big dull dud.
钱德真的太棒了
Chandler is fantastic.
- 什么   - 天啊 你知道一拍即合吗
- What?     - Oh, God. You know how people just click?
他来家里接我 我一开门就觉得心动
Like, he came by to pick me up. I opened the door, and it was just like, "click."
- 他有跟你说吗   - 那个嘛…
- Did he tell you?     - Well...
他真的很好心 他是个好心人吧
Oh, and he's got such a good heart. Doesn't he have a good heart?
我知道 他真的好体贴
Oh, I know. And he's so sweet.
他说他会打电话来 直接帮我接到办公室
He said he'd call, so put him straight through.
- 这真的很棒吧   - 别扫兴
- Isn't this great?     - Don't spoil it.
来吧 宝贝 别走 求求你
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
你觉得呢
What do you say?
喂
Hello? Oh!
是你 等一下
It's you. Just, uh... Just one sec.
我得接这通电话
I am going to take this call.
等一下 我希望在舞台上
When I continue, I hope that there will appear on-stage...
可以看到魔法 在剧场界我们称之为
...this magical thing that in the theater we call...
入戏
...committing to the moment.
这家伙跟卡通人物一样
The guy's like a cartoon.
你到底看上他哪一点
What do you see in him, anyway?
他非常聪明
He happens to be brilliant.
比跟你约会的毛衣女好多了
Which is more than I can say for that sweater you're dating.
我对她的毛衣没兴趣
Hey, I'm not interested in her sweater.
重要的是毛衣下面的东西
It's what's underneath her sweater that counts.
而且…
And besides, since, uh...
你干嘛在乎我跟谁约会
Since when do you care who I'm going out with?
我不在乎 为什么 你要我在乎吗
I don't care. Why? Do you want me to care?
你要我希望你在乎吗
Heh. Do you want me to want you to care?
是吗
Do you?
什么
What?
好吧 恐怕我得这么做 从刚刚中断那里开始
Okay. I'm afraid to say this, but let's pick it up where we left off.
来吧 宝贝 别走 求求你 你觉得呢
Come on, baby, don't go. Please? What do you say?
我没有留下来的理由
I've got no reason to stay.
停
Stop.
停 你们必须停下来
Stop it. You must stop.
你们都是烂演员
You are bad actors.
这是出烂戏
This is a terrible play.
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
我不敢相信再过一星期我们就要演出
I can't believe we go on in a week.
一定不会有问题的
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
既然提早收工 你要去画马克杯吗
So since we're getting off early, do you want to go and paint mugs?
什么
What?
昨晚我跟你提过的那个地方
You know, at that place I told you about last night?
对 画马克杯
Oh, yeah, with the mug-painting. Yeah.
我有注意听
I was so listening to that.
你知道吗 我想今晚我得练习一下
But, uh, you know what? I think I need to work on my stuff tonight.
- 好的   - 好的
- Oh, okay.     - Okay.
- 明天见   - 好的
- I'll see you tomorrow.     - Okay.
- 好的   - 晚安
- Okay. Ha, ha.     - Night.
你没事吧
Uh, are you okay?
我想应该没事
Yeah, I guess.
我们该如何演这场戏
Like, what are we gonna do about the scene, huh?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Well, um...
或许我们该激烈一点
Maybe if it had more heat.
你是什么意思
Well, how do you mean?
安德丽娜在找理由留下来 对吧
Well, Adrianne's looking for a reason to stay, right?
维多不能只是吻她 他必须…
Victor can't just kiss her. He's gotta...
他必须给她一个理由 你知道吗
He's gotta really give her a reason, you know?
或许他可以跟她舌吻
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
或许…
Or maybe...
或许他可以抓住她 把她抱起来
Maybe he could grab her and lift her up.
对 安德丽娜用脚环住他的腰
Yeah, yeah. Then Adrianne, maybe she could wrap her legs around his waist.
然后她撕开他的衬衫 亲他的胸膛跟肚子
And then she could rip off his shirt and kiss his chest and his stomach.
他可以用他的牙齿扯开她的洋装
And then he could use his teeth, his teeth, to undo her dress and...
还要咬她
And bite her.
这场戏结束时他可以占有她
And then right when the scene ends, he could take her...
发挥他的原始兽性
...with this raw, animal...
就像那样吗
Something like that?
对 差不多跟我想的一样
Yeah, that's pretty much what I had in mind.
- 对   - 对
- Yeah.     - Yeah.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
现在喝酒太早了
It's a little early to be drinking.
我终于跟凯特更进一步了
Things, uh, finally happened with Kate.
- 你在开玩笑 太棒了   - 太棒了
- Oh. That's great.     - You're kidding. That's great.
那真的很棒
Oh, it was so amazing.
跟她做爱后…
After the lovemaking...
天啊
Oh, my.
我看着她沉睡 一 看就好几个小时
I just watched her sleep for, like, hours.
她只是在吸气
Just breathing in...
吐气
...and breathing out.
我知道她在做梦 因为她的眼睛是这样的
And I knew she was dreaming because her eyes kept going like this:
我得说乔安娜误会了 好吗
I'm telling you, Joanna's got it all wrong, okay?
我只是说"这真的很好玩 我们有空再出来"
All I said was, "This was fun. Let's do it again sometime.
"我会打电话给你"
I'll give you a call."
不知道为什么 她以为你会打电话给她
I wonder why she thinks you're going to call her?
约会后就得那么说
That's what you say at the end of a date.
你就不能说"幸会 晚安"吗
You can't just say, "Nice to meet you. Good night"?
当她的面说
To her face?
那时我们结束约会 我站在那里
It's the end of the date, I'm standing there...
她等着我说我会打电话给她
...she's waiting for me to say I'll call her...
我只是脱口而出 无法控制自己
...and it just, you know, comes out. I can't help it.
那是一时冲动
It's a compulsion.
别这样 瑞秋 男人说他会打电话
Come on, Rach, when a guy says he's gonna call...
不代表他一定会打
...it doesn't mean he's going to call.
你没遇过那种事吗
This never happened to you?
他们一向会打电话来
Well, they always called.
该死
Bite me.
- 他有打电话来吗   - 没有 抱歉
- Did he call?     - No, sorry.
为什么 他说他会打电话 为什么他没打
Why? Why? He said he'd call. Why hasn't he called?
或许他害怕聪明 坚强 成功的女强人
Maybe he's intimidated by really smart, strong, successful women.
苏菲 拜托你别拍我马屁
Sophie, will you please climb out of my butt.
- 为什么他不打来 瑞秋   - 好吧
- Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why?     - Okay, okay.
或许他觉得很怪 因为你是我的上司
Um, well, uh, maybe he feels awkward because you are my boss.
为什么他要觉得怪
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
该觉得怪的人是你
The only person that should feel awkward is you.
你没有叫他别打电话来 对吧
You didn't tell him not to call me?
如果你不喜欢你朋友跟你老板约会
If you're uncomfortable with your friend dating someone you work for...
总是有办法可以解决这问题的
...there are always ways to fix that.
立刻打电话给她
Call her. Call her now.
我的手被割伤了
Multiple, so many paper cuts.
为什么他不打电话来 瑞秋
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why? Why?
我不了解 他说他会打电话的 为什么…
I don't understand. He said he'd call."
钱德 我得说她抓狂了 她发疯了
Chandler, I'm telling you, she's flipped out. She's gone crazy.
那么把电话给我吧
Oh. Well, give me the phone, then.
这一点都不好玩 她觉得你没打电话都是我的错
This isn't funny. She thinks it's my fault you haven't called her.
你分须打电话给她
You have to call her.
听着 隔了这么久 你不能打电话跟对方说
Look, you can't call somebody after this long just to say:
"如果你没发现 我不喜欢你"
"In case you didn't notice, I don't like you."
那么你得再约她出去
Then you're gonna have to take her out again.
不 她真的很无趣 而且她的眼角
No. She's really dull, and she gets this...
还积着睫毛膏留下的污渍
...gross mascara-goop thing in the corner of her eye.
我不在乎
I don't care. I don't care.
你得再约她出去做个了断
You'll take her out again and end it...
让她知道你们真的没希望
...and end it in a way that she knows it's actually ended.
我不知道这对你来说有多难 别再跟她说你会打电话给她
And I don't care how hard it is for you. Do not tell her you'll call her again.
好吧
All right, fine.
只是一次午餐约会 从现在开始我会自己追女生
But it's just a lunch date. From now on, I get my own dates.
我不要你再帮我牵红线了
I don't want you setting me up with anybody again.
没问题
That's fine.
- 我只是在说大话 你知道的   - 我知道
- That's just a lot of big talk, you know.     - I know.
摩妮卡
Mon?
我在浴室
I'm in the shower.
失火了…
Aah! Fire. There's a fire. Fire.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi.
我跟萝伦说过了 我跟她提了我们的事
So I, uh, talked to Lauren. I kind of told her how things were with us.
你跟马歇尔说了吗
Did you, uh...? Did you talk to Marshall?
说什么
About what?
你知道的 我们之间的事
Ha, ha. You know, about what happened with us.
没有
No.
没理由让他知道
And there's really no reason why he should find out.
我们不要小题大做 好吗
So, uh, let's not make a big deal out of it, okay?
你是什么意思
What are you talking about?
这件事很重要
It was a big deal.
少来了 你不能跟我说昨晚的事对你来说毫无意义
I mean, come on, you can't tell me last night didn't mean something to you.
我也在场 你的演技没那么厉害
I was there. You're not that good an actress.
听着
Look.
我只是一时意乱情迷
Um, I was... I was just caught up in the moment.
就那样
That's all it was.
乔伊 我很遗憾让你伤心
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad...
你没跟你在乎她 多过于她在乎你的女人上床过
...but haven't you ever slept with a woman where it meant more to her than to you?
没有
No.
- 嗨 凯特   - 嗨 萝伦
- Hi, Kate.     - Hi, Lauren.
嗨 萝伦
Hi, Lauren.
嗨 猪猡
Hi, pig.
抱歉 我吓到你了
Sorry I, uh... I scared you in there.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
对了
By the way...
我只是在检查莲蓬头的按摩功能
...I was just checking the shower massager.
对
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
我打电话到你工作的地方找你
I tried to reach you at work.
今生了火灾
There's been a fire.
什么 天啊
What? Oh, my... Oh, my God.
发生了什么事
What happened?
我们相信起火点在这里
Well, we believe it originated here...
就在芬芳疗室
...in the Aroma Room.
好吧 大家都逃出来了吗
All right, did everyone get out okay?
长颈鹿跟海盗都没事
Well, the giraffe's okay and so is the pirate.
- 这是什么   - 不 菲比别看
- What is this?     - No, Phoebe, don't look.
你不会想看那个的
You don't want to see what's under there.
寄宿小狗
The foster puppets.
没什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
它只是…一直都积在这里
It's just... It's right here, and it's all the time.
谢谢你请我吃午餐
Well, thanks again for lunch.
- 对 很愉快   - 真的 没错吧
- Yes, this was pleasant.     - It was, wasn't it?
- 那里的食物很好吃   - 可不是吗
- The food there was great.     - Wasn't it?
保重
So take care.
你也是
You too.
这真的太棒了 我会打电话给你 我们再出去吃饭
This was great. I'll give you a call. We should do it again.
太棒了 我很期待
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
- 瑞秋 有留言吗   - 在苏菲的桌上
- Rachel, any messages?     - Sophie's desk.
钱德 你要打电话给她吗
Chandler. Are you gonna call her?
- 不   - 钱德
- No.     - Chandler.
听着 对不起 我软弱 可悲又抱歉
Look, I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak and pathetic and sorry.
好 你得立刻告诉她
Okay, you are gonna tell her. You're gonna tell her now.
我不会打电话给你
Ow, I'm not gonna call you.
什么
What?
对不起
I'm sorry.
抱歉我说我会打电话给你 我根本就不想打
I'm sorry that I said I was going to when I'm not.
听着 这跟你无关
Ugh. Look, this has nothing to do with you.
这不是瑞秋的错 都是我的错
And this isn't Rachel's fault. It's me.
提到女人 我有很严重的问题
I have serious, serious problems when it comes to women.
我害怕承诺 亲密
I have issues with commitment, intimacy...
睫毛膏污渍
...mascara goop.
真的很抱歉 这是行不通的
And I'm really sorry. It's just that this is not... This isn't gonna work out.
这跟我希望的结局不同
Well, this isn't how I was hoping this would end...
我想我得感激你的诚实
...but I guess I have to appreciate your honesty.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
So...
这真的太棒了 我会打电话给你 我们再约时间见面
Well, this is great. I'll give you a call. We should do it again sometime.
贝丝 我的意思是
Wha... So anyway, Beth, what I'm saying is...
那晚我跟你回家前 我该考虑到你的感受
...I should have considered your feelings before I went home with you that night.
我…
I've, uh...
最近我能体会你的感觉
I've recently learned what it's like to be on your side of it...
对不起
...and I'm sorry.
你能原谅我吗
So do you think you can forgive me?
太棒了 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
好吧 再见
Okay. Bye.
喂 珍妮佛
Hello, Jennifer?
洛瑞欧太太 珍妮佛在吗
Oh, hi, Mrs. Laurio. Is Jennifer there?
她不在家吗
Oh, she's not home, huh?
事实上我也得跟你谈一谈
Well, uh, actually I kind of need to talk to you too.